ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files /4283
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files
1994-2008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
/4283
208.11 cubic feet
208.1 linear ft.
Records (documents), case files.
8159472
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
D Cohen, June 17, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 05, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4283 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Audio-Visual Materials /4283 MB: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Memorabilia /4283 P: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Photographs /4283/001: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Files /4283/001 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Audio- Visual Materials /4283/001 MB: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Memorabilia /4283/001 PUBS: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Publications /4283/001 (d): ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Born Digital Material /4283/002: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Files /4283/002 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Audio-Visual Materials /4283/002 P: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Photographs
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.)
8159472
- Administration Program Files. (Box 1)
  - Contract Language: Working 03W037 Public 4/28/05 HENDERSON/REBHOLZ, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - L-M Strategies 04W032 Public Henderson 10/26/04, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - SHRM Online Public Program 2/9/04-4/19/04 03W063 Henderson, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - SHRM (Classroom) Public 9/15-12/1/03 03W011 Henderson (Folder 1 of 2), 2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - SHRM (Classroom) Public 9/15-12/1/03 03W011 Henderson (Folder 2 of 2), 2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Discipline and Grievance Procedures Public 5/1/01 and 5/2/01 00W169 Grogan, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Charlie Morre, BEW 662-611, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - For Review, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - ATSD-Learning Tech. for Improving Perf. American Society for Training and Development 2/13-4/10/2001 00W087 Grogan, 2000- 2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Increasing Effectiveness in Arb. Public 9/17-9/19/03 03W015 HENDERSON/REBHOLZ, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Prep for Collective Bargaining Public 9/23-9/24/03 03W017 HENDERSON/REBHOLZ, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Western Region Activity Report and Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA) Update, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Stwd Mgmt and Mgmt I/E Reports, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 2003 SWMG I+E Stmts. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - SHRM Certificate Program, Invoice and Other Docs., 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Human Resources and the Law Public 3/28/2001 - 3/20/2001 00W136 Grogan (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - The Investigatory Grievance Public 5/3/2001 ooW150 Grogan (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Western Region Program Activity Report and Other Docs., 2001 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Public Labor Relations Law 3/26/01 and 3/27/01 00W163 Grogan, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Preparation for Coll. Bargaining Public 4/25/2001 00W167 Grogan (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Selecting and Designating Performance Improvement Interventions, Inclement Weather Policy and Income and Expense Report, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Scope and Contents
    Selecting and Designating Performance Improvement Interventions- slight damage (wrinkled)
  - Costing Out the Coll. Barg. Agreement Public 4/26/2001 Agreement 00W168 Grogan (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Effective Interviewing Public 10/4/00 and 10/5/00 00W034 Grogan, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Supervising and Managing People Public 11/30/00 - 12/1/00 00W040 Grogan, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Learning Technologies for Improving Performance, Standard Voucher, Notice of Pending Payment, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Administration Historical Files; Peer/ Policy Review/ Degree Programs & Other Committees; Staff Meetings, ORG charts, Committees, PIR, Dist. Highlights. (Box 2)
  - Purchase Order Requests + Receipts, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Mission of the ILR School, 1991-2002 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Clippings damaged (ripped, torn) around edges
  - Outside Review, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - PAFS, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Photos, 1998-2002 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Pamphlet and Book Listings, 1961-1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Peer Review Procedure, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Performance Systems International, Inc. PSI/ CIT/ FISC, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Policies- Extension Procedure, 1953-1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Policies - Faculty Personnel, 1961-1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Policies- Advisory Committee on Personnel, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Procedure manual Workshop Details, 1972-1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Project 2000, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Program Pricing Policies (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Pre-Retirement, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Final Report Pre-Retirement Dissemination Project #149100-77-901-38 1976-1977 + Booklets: The Money Manager and Let's Talk About Money, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Pre-Retirement Dissemination Project #610176-78-901-38 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Publicity/ Promotional (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes (Folder 1 of 2), 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes (Folder 1 of 2), 1998-2002 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1998-2002 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Support Staff Meetings, 1992-1998 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Reports from Planning Committee on Future Extension Planning and Outside Review Panel, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Documents Relating to Extension Staff (Folder 1 of 2), 1992-2002 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Documents Relating to Extension Staff (Folder 2 of 2), 1992-1997 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Documents Relating to the Office Workplace (Folder 1 of 2), 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Documents Relating to the Office Workplace (Folder 2 of 2), 1993-2000 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Administration Historical Files; Peer/ Policy Review/ Degree Programs & Other Committees; Staff Meetings, ORG charts, Committees, PIR, Distr highlights. (Box 3)
  - Employment Maintenance UAW/Ford Chicago 2/19/01-2/23/01 00W118 Fleron (Folder 1 of 2), 2001 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Employment Maintenance UAW/Ford Chicago 2/19/01-2/23/01 00W118 Fleron (Folder 2 of 2), 2001 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Employment Maintenance UAW/Ford-Detroit 1/22/01-1/26/01 00W117A Fleron (Folder 1 of 2), 2001 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Employment Maintenance UAW/Ford-Detroit 1/22/01-1/26/01 00W117A Fleron (Folder 2 of 2), 2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Documents Relating to Administrative Professionals (Folder 1 of 4), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Documents Relating to Administrative Professionals (Folder 2 of 4), 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Documents Relating to Administrative Professionals (Folder 3 of 4), 2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Documents Relating to Administrative Professionals: Registration Form Extension Division (Folder 4 of 4) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Contract Language Public 9/14/04 04W030 Henderson, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Dynamics of Labor Negotiations Public 11/1/04 04W033 Henderson, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Interest Based Statewide Management Certificate Program 10/23 - 10/24/2002 Bargaining 02W007, 1999-2002 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Building Better W/P Relationships American Axle 9/23/99 99W044 Henderson, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Building Better W/P Relationships American Axle 9/9/99 CANCELED 99W042 Henderson, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Building Better W/P Relationships American Axle 9/2/99 99W041 Henderson, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Building Better W/P Relationships American Axle 8/2/99 99W040 Henderson, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Building Better W/P Relationships American Axle 8/19/99 99W039 Henderson (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Building Better W/P Relationships American Axle 8/12/99 99W038 Henderson, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Building Better W/P Relationships American Axle 8//99 99W037 Henderson, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Employment Maintenance UAW-Ford- BLACK LAKE 3/5/00-3/8/00 9W111, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Blacklake 99W111 3/5-3/9/00 Certificates, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - AIS Detroit 2/21-2/25/00 99W110, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 99W112- St. Louis Registrations 3/27-3/31/00, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Strategic Implications for Western District and Memorandum- Strategic Planning Report, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Testimonial Dinners, ETC., 1975-1990 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Union Organizing Info/ Cornell Strike Policy and Related Information, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Vacation/ Sick leave, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Who We Are.. What We Do.. On the Scene in Western New York, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Western District Highlights, 1960-2002 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Western District - Historical File, 1960-1985 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Some documents (Newspaper) are ripped
- Faculty-Woods, Susan; Workplace Diversity, Mutual Gains;. (Box 4)
  - Collective Bargaining, 1986-1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - COIB IAM 1053 Labor Programs in Buffalo, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Past Practice, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Duty of Fair Representation, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Legal Rts of Stewards Labor Programs in Buffalo, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - TUE 340- Oleam 1986 Labor Programs in Buffalo (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - IBEW Local 1352- Macie Addams, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - L konwruas #576 Labor Programs in Buffalo, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - RLA - Iam Local Lodge 75 Labor Programs in Buffalo, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - OPEIA 212, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - JESPA Labor Programs in Buffalo, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Public Sector of Training USWA Local 14051, 15071, 15315, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - CME in Public Sector, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Keeping Count for Your Union Illness and Injury Documentation, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Establishing A Toxic Substance Information Program, 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Employer Compliance Training, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Part I + IV: New York State Right to Know Law and Occupational Exposure to Toxic Substances, 1979-1986 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - CWA- Test Taking Skills, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - JTPA, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - JTPA and Job Training Opportunities for Women and Women Workers in Western New York: Employment, Unemployment and Effective Reemployment Strategies, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - CWA- The Crisis in Health Care, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Health Care Cost Containment, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Worker Access to Info Labor Programs in Buffalo, 1980-1985 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Establishing A Toxic Substance Information Program, 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - MSDS- Tool to Workers' Health Chemical Hazard Information, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Military Spending on the Rise, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - In Our Hands- Women and Tech., 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - ACTWU Women's Prog May 1988 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - EEO in Declining Economy, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Computer Basics Labor Programs in Buffalo, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Facilitator's Guide (revised), 1986-1990 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Workplace Literacy, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - "Fast for Life" Kit WNY Grape Boycott Coalition, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Reproductive Hazards, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Workplace Reproductive Health or Parents and Children, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Asbestos Conference, 1981-1985 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Occupational Stress, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Ed Baldwin- Surviving Unemployment, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Structural Unemployment, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Kaleck- Politics of FE, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Notes O'Connor The Corporations and the State (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Baron and Sweezy- Mandel Mono Capt and Related Items, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Useful Macro- Ec Notes, 1975-1979 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Costing Contracts Lab Research Fall 79, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Wage Th- Lab Ec Sample Syllabus, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Corporate Financial Statements How to Research Corp., 1987 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Brochures. (Box 5)
  - From box #421- Misc. ILR Pamphlets, 1991-1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Reflections on Progress at Work, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Different ILR Booklets/ Pamphlets, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - ILR Pamphlets Related to Public Workshops, Unions, Supervisory Studies Graduate Studies etc.., 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - ILR Pamphlets: Buffalo Labor Studies and Others Related to Labor, 1995-1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Cornell ILR Pamphlets: Human Resources, Employee Management etc.., 1995-2003 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Docs. Related to ILR: Management Development + Human Resources Workshops in Ithaca and Other Workshops, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Booklets about Workshops related to the ILR School, 1995-2001 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Workshops and Programs: Human Resources Equal Employment Opportunities Management Development, 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Workshops and Programs ILR: Management Development Human Resources Equal Employment Opportunities Labor Relations, 2000- 2001 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Misc. ILR Booklets Related to Unions, Negotiation, and Human Resources, 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - ILR Workshops, 1994-2000 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - ILR Pamphlets Related to Different Programs, 1989-1999 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - ILR Management Programs, 1991-1997 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Misc. ILR Booklets, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Extension Outreach, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - ILR Documents: Pamphlets and Other Papers, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - ILR Mgn Programs, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - ILR Programs, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Flyers, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - ILR Documents Related to Different Trainings and Dedication of Building, 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - ILR: A Workplace Education Resource of Today For Tomorrow, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - ILR School of Industrial and Labor Relations, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Faculty-Woods, Susan; Workplace Diversity, Mutual Gains. (Box 6)
  - Documents Related to Disability Management and The American Psychological Association, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Opportunities for Collaboration in and Among Erie County Schools, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Susan Woods - WDN, 1994-1995 (1) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Susan Woods-WDN 1994-1995 (2) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - ILR- Employment in Europe: A Practitioner's Guide to Setting Up Business in Europe, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Japan Conference, 1978-1982 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Clarkson- Correspondence, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - AirCo- Carbon-OCAW Final Report, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Innovative Funds Proposal, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - NY state Small Contractors Association, 1970-1984 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Military Spending, 1979-1988 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - IUE- Gowanda Electric Local 306, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - HERE 26- Housing Trust, 1988-1991 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - The Union Neighborhood Assistance Corporation's Comprehensive Housing Program, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - UAW Local 55- and d Instit, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 1989 Airline Stk- 1 AM, 1978-1989 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Fighting the Economic Assault on Labor, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Concess Barg 1983 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Threats to Collective Bargaining, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Women Political Skills- Leadership Union, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Managing a Political Campaign, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - A Workbook for the 1984 Presidential Election New York State AFL-CIO (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - 1 on 1 Campaign, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Arbitration Skills Niagara Plant Employees Union, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Local Union Officers Training, 1979-1984 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Cliff Leadership IBEW 2154 Labor Programs in Buffalo, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Defending and Promoting Unionism, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Parliamentary Procedure Labor Programs in Buffalo, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Parliamentary Procedure Labor Programs in Buffalo, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Effective Writing Skills for Trade, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Dunkirk Union Communication, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Surviving Unemployment at Dunkirk, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Program manuals- SHRM slides. (Box 7)
  - BHAG Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Administration Program Files. (Box 8)
  - Building Better W/P Relationships American Axle 9/30/99 99W045 Henderson, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Organizational Change VA Medical Center 99W046 Henderson Cancelled, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Organizational Change VA Medical Center Cancelled 99W047 Henderson, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Organizational Change VA Medical Center 99W048 Henderson Cancelled, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Employment Maintenance - AIS UAW-Ford NPC 99W049 9/26/99-10/1/99 Fleron Regional, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Office Depot Accounts Payable 7/1/99-6/30/00, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Continuous Quality Improvement VA Medical School 99W050 Henderson Cancelled, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Diversity Workshop UB School of Medicine 99W051 8/12/99 Henderson, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Diversity Workshop UB School of Medicine 99W052 8/16/99 Henderson, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Gross Domestic Product vs. Quality of Life (Betty Friedan) Public 10/29/99 99W053 Rebholz, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - NLRB and the National Labor Relations Act, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Conference Topics, and Documents Related to the NLRB, 1993-2000 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - NLRB/Cornell 2000 Cornell ILR/NLRB 5/19/2000 99W054 Campagna (Folder 1 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - NLRB/Cornell 2000 Cornell ILR/NLRB 5/19/2000 99W054 Campagna (Folder 2 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Documents Related to NLRB Brochures, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Organizational Success thu Employee Appreciation 9/12/99 99W055 Fleron, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Sexual Harassment Plumbers Local #22 5/10/2000 99W057 Lipsitz (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Manufacturing Leadership Development Assessment and Skills NABISCO 9/1/99; 9/30/99; 10/1/99 99W056 Henderson (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Positive Mental Attitude Erie City Assoc. of Ed. Office Prof. 10/06/99 99W058 Rebholz, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Harvest of Change Niag Cty Dept of Mental Health 20/27/99 99W059 Grogan, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Problems and Prospects for a New Century PERB and Cornell University 10/29/99 99W060 Campagna, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Documents Related to PERB and the Taylor Law and the NLRB, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - PERB 99W060, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - PERB and the Taylor Law (Folder 1 of 2), 1999 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Economic Education-A Chinese Case Study Cornell University 99W061 9/10/99 Fleron, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Sunrise Breakfast Series (ADA update) Cornell University/Public 99W062 11/4/99 Grogan/Campagna, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Building Better Workplace Relationships American Axle 99W063 9/20/99 Henderson, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Building Better W/P Relationships American Axle 10/7/99 99W064 Henderson, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Building Better W/P Relationships American Axle 10/14/99 99W065 Henderson, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Building Better W/P Relationships American Axle 10/21/99 99W066 Henderson (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - PERB and the Taylor Law (Folder 2 of 2), 1999 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Administration Program Files. (Box 9)
  - Building Better W/P Relationships American Axle 10/28/99 99W067 Henderson, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Building Better W/P Relationships American Axle 99W068 11/4/9 Henderson, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Building Better W/P Relationships American Axle 11/11/99 99W069 Henderson (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Building better W/P Relationships American Axle 11/18/99 99W070 Henderson Cancelled, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Building better W/P Relationships American Axle12/2/99 99W071 Henderson, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Building better W/P Relationships American Axle 12/9/99 99W072 Henderson, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Lifestyle Management - Train the Trainer UAW-Ford 10/18/99 - 10/21/99 99W073 Suggs (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Lifestyle 99W073 BL 10/18-21/99, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - WNY AFL-CIO Economic Group 99W074 AFL-CIO Buffalo Council Buffalo 9/14/99 Lipsitz, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Labor Forum 2000 Public Program/Cornell University Buffalo 12/3/99 99W075 Lipsitz, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Program Consultation Mountview Health Facility Buffalo 9/13/99 99W076 Suggs, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - '99 Fall Conference A. Philip Randolph Institute Buffalo 10/16/99 99W077 Suggs, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Tech Assist Freezer Queens Food, Inc. Buffalo, NY 8/22/99 99W078 Henderson Cancelled, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Tech Assist-Design Buffalo State College 8/1-9/30/99 99W079 Henderson, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Intro Buffalo Labor Studies Carpenters Labor #9 10/6/99 99W080 Lipsitz, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Discussion of Leadership Institute WNY-AFL-CIO Econ. Dev. Group 5/4/00 99W081 Lipsitz, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Sunrise Breakfast -Emp Liab Cornell University Buffalo, NY 12/9/99 99W082 Grogan, 1983-1999 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - E2 Ed for Employment NOMMOS 10/25-10/29/99 99W083 Fleron, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Finance for Non-Financial Managers Public 3/22/2000+3/23/2000 99W084 Henderson, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Union Pension Plans: A Primer Carpenters Local #9 3/5/2000 99W0815 Lipsitz, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Manufacturing Leadership Skills Nabisco 99W086 A+B Henderson, 1995-2000 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Tech Asst: Mediation Buchanan Ingersol 9/28, 9/30 10/6/99 99W087 Campagna, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Alternative Dispute Resolution in the W/P Employee Relations Association 10/12/99 99W088 Campagna, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Effective Interviewing Techniques AFT-CIO-Econ. Development Groups 10/14/99 99W089 Lipsitz, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Strategy and Tactics of Collective Bargaining American Federation of Teachers Local 4834 11/12/99 99W090 Lipsitz, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Building better W/P Relationships American Axle and Manufacturing 11/12/99 and 11/25/2000 99W091 A+13 Henderson, 1999- 2000 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Building Better W/P Relationships American Axle and Manufacturing 12/16/99 99W092 Henderson Cancelled, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Labor and Film Hallwalls 2/123/00 99W093 Lipsitz, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Labor and Film Hallwalls 3/10/00 99W094 Lipsitz, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Labor and Film Hallwall 4/28/2000 99W095 Lipsitz, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Presentation of AFL-CIO Group PACE/ Niag. City. Legislature 10/27/99 99W096 Lipsitz, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - SHRM Certification Public 2/7/00 - 4/17/00 99W097 Grogan, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Report: Work on Econ Develop Group AFL-CIO Council 9/14/99 99W098 Lipsitz, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Common Sense Economics for Labor CWA #14177/Derby, NY 12/2/99 99W099, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Using Instruments to Init. Org. Chg. 99W100 Summit Educational Resources/Tonawanda, NY 11/12/99 Henderson, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Writing Performance Plans-Sup. NFTA 12/2/99 and 12/15/99 99W101 Henderson, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Team Building for Success Buffalo Public Schools Library 2/19/00 99W102 Rebholz, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 37)